featsocks.com 2018-09-08

# Privacy Policy – FEAT Socks

Home » Privacy Policy

FEAT Socks operates the website located at www.FEATsocks.com. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect through our website and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@featsocks.com.

**The Types of Information that We Collect**

We collect your email address if you sign up for our newsletter. We reserve the right to use your email address and any other personally identifiable information that you provide to us to respond to you and to send you marketing materials for our own products and services. We will not share your information with outside parties who wish to market other products and services to you.

Like most websites, our website may incorporate “pixel tags”, “web beacons”, or similar tracking technologies and “cookies” that allow us to track the actions of visitors of our website. Pixel tags and cookies are used to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the name of your internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, the date and time you access our website, the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our website, the website address, if any, to which you travel from our website, your home page customization preferences and other similar traffic-related information. We may aggregate your information with similar data collected from other visitors to help us improve our website and the products, services, applications, content and features that we provide through our website. We do not use non-personally identifiable information in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or collect personally identifiable information from you.

**How We Use the Information We Gather**

Generally, we will not disclose the personally identifiable information that we collect through your use of our website to unaffiliated third parties. We reserve the right, however, to provide such information to our employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to perform certain services for us, including distributing advertisements and other marketing materials on our behalf. We also reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information that we collect to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following reasons: (i) to comply with the law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect, or prosecute criminal offenses or attacks on the technical integrity of our website or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, safety and security of FEAT Socks and its employees, our website visitors, and/or the public.

**Our Website may Contain Links to Other Websites**

Please be aware that we are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any websites that you access through our website and that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which we collect through our website. We encourage you to ensure that you read the privacy statements of all the destination websites which you visit.

**We Reserve the Right to Update and Revise this Privacy Policy at Any Time**

From time to time we review this Privacy Policy to ensure that it complies with applicable law. Consequently, we reserve the right to update and revise this Privacy Policy at any time. You will know if this Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit to the website by referring to the "Effective Date of Current Policy" date at the bottom of this page. Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us from time to time, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are aware of its terms.
